{
    "id": "c908cde9141a4e308a2ff7f68f794ee8",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I was waiting ......................... the bus stop when I met Larry.",
            "description": "We use at to talk about position at a place. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Is there any milk .............................. the bottle?",
            "description": "In is used for position inside three-dimensional spaces. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at",
                "under"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was .......................... my way to work when I met with an accident.",
            "description": "On the way means during the journey.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Please don't stand in the door - you are .......................... my way.",
            "description": "In the / my way is used for obstacles. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no way ............................ proving that he was lying.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "of",
                "for",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has acted ............................ several movies.",
            "description": "The correct expression is 'act in movies'.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you put the meat ........................ the fridge?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven't seen her after she moved ......................... Canada.",
            "description": "We use 'to' to indicate direction. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you put the child .......................... bed?",
            "description": "To put someone to bed is to make them go to bed. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "into",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The President will appear ........................ television tonight.",
            "description": "The correct expressions are on the radio, on television and on the phone.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We want the meeting to start exactly ......................... time.",
            "description": "If something happens on time, it happens at the planned time. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She decided to quit her job ........................ several reasons.",
            "description": "We use 'for' before reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}